I caught
astray from that interview Amanda seals
spoke in regards
to uh isay uh-huh I had already shot
isay
okay the trajectory of that interview of
Club
Shay made Issa and her team not want to
put out our show so I have not put out
out of respect ah it's a dominant effect
yes had knowing what I know now I wish I
would have I wish your interview would
have happened and then she would had an
opportunity to because I see from Issa
side it was image control right
interview by the when we did issa's
interview Amanda's interview it wasn't
posted yet right so I didn't want to do
her a disservice but with that being
said Isa please let's run it back